What's going on everybody? Laura Tech
here with another node pack for you
guys. This one is the AI image prompt
builder and the AI prompt library. So
jumping right into it, there are two
nodes that are in this custom node pack
as I just mentioned. And by the end of
the video, I will show you why this node
has more possible prompt combinations
than there are atoms in the observable
universe and I'm not exaggerating. Quick
disclaimer just to get it out of the way
earlier, this node pack does not work
with nodes 2.0 enabled, but it doesn't
matter anyway because nodes 2.0 is ugly
and nobody should be using it. So as
long as you keep that off, everything
below works exactly as shown. If you're
wanting to know where you can get this
node pack, this node pack is available
along with my other custom node packs,
some private workflows, and more coming
soon on my Patreon for paid members. The
link is in the description. Also in the
description is my Discord for one-on-one
coaching and my RunPod referral link. If
you've never used RunPod before and you
want to use cloud GPU services at a
minimum of $10 through it and you get $5
for free. So what this prompt builder
does is replaces typing prompts by hand.
As you can see here, if I expand these
two sections, we have our categories and
subcategories.
And in the categories, we have a bunch
of different things such as body, face,
hair, and clothing, pose, background.
Basically everything that makes up all
of the aspects of an image. And then
within the subcategories, say we go to
body, there are things like skin tone,
body type, height, waist, hips, all of
that. And that is the same for every one
of these subcategories. So you can go
through and pick all of the settings
that you want to make up your own
character or you can use your own
character LORA attached, which I will
show you how to do right now. So you can
see here I expand the character and LORA
panel. It sits at the top of the node
regardless of which mode you're in,
whether you're in professional /
business or the influencer section. So
there are obviously things here like the
trigger word, a drop-down list of LORAs,
the LORA strength that you can dial in
here, the clip strength, and a list of
your already saved characters. Now just
another disclaimer, if you are using a
character LORA, what you'll need to do
is wire your diffusion model into this
node and your clip text encoder into
this node as well. And then take the
wiring outputs of these and feed them
into your workflow. So, if I drop down
the list of categories here, we can see
that there is a character section. And
what I'm going to do is just add the
trigger word to one of my LoRAs
from the drop-down list.
I'm going to select the LoRA and then
I'm going to click save.
It will ask if you want to save, so I
just click yes here.
And now we can see that we have loaded
our LoRA. And you can also change the
picture of each of the LoRAs that you
have saved in here. So, you can see here
that I've just selected a picture for my
character. Assuming that I have that
enabled, it will apply my LoRA to all of
my prompt generations. So, now let's
move on to the difference between the
two main categories. We have
professional/business and influencer.
The professional/business section is
built for commercial or product style
photos, editorial photos,
straightforward portrait work, and so
on. And moving on to the influencer tab,
it's the same core idea, but
restructured for social media or creator
style content where physical
presentation matters a lot more. The
influencer section has a lot more
categories and subcategories, especially
in the clothing section, the
backgrounds, and also the influencer
section gives you the ability to
completely customize the face,
body, hair, makeup, and so on. So, most
of you are probably going to find more
use in the influencer section, but for
people who do want to create product
displays for their stuff, you can use
the professional/business section. The
reason they're separated is because
influencer style content needs way more
granularity on appearance and setting
than a single subject for just a product
display or something like that. You also
have the full customizability to add
your own categories and add your own
subcategories as you please.
I'm going to quickly collapse these two
sections here to show you the
customizability of every list. So, real
quick, we're in the pose section, and
then you can see in the subcategory
section of posing, there's a bunch of
different generalized types of poses.
So, let me condense those real quick.
So, if you're wanting to rearrange the
order in which things are arranged in
these lists, you can drag and drop them
however you please. You can right click
them, you can delete, edit, or add
thumbnails to them. So, this allows for
full control and customizability over
whatever it is that you're wanting to
create. You can literally add whatever
you want. This is completely
customizable. And now, let's say that
you don't want to go through and
pick every single category and
subcategory option. There is this
randomizer section. So, there's a few
different options in here. You can
randomize everything completely, but
obviously you don't want to do that if
you have a character lore attached. So,
what you can also do is pick all of the
physical aspects of, let's say, a
character that you don't have a lore
for. This randomizer option will leave
physical appearance untouched, so things
like age, ethnicity, gender, body, face,
hair, and randomize everything else,
such as outfit, pose, scene, camera, and
lighting. And then, the randomize with
lore section resets all the physical
appearance fields, like age, ethnicity,
and so on, to empty, and then randomizes
everything else while it includes your
lore trigger word in the prompt. So,
nothing conflicts with a character
lore's trained look. And then, there's
also a custom preset where you can go
through and just select every single
thing that you want to randomize, too,
as well, if you want to do that. I
assume most of you are going to be using
a character lore with this, so I will
select randomize with lore. And then,
you want to randomize the seed here of
the generation that you get, so every
generation is different. So, the
randomize with lore option has been
selected. So, let's run this, and we can
see here that we have our output text
over here in this previous text, but
there's also a support node that is
added with this node pack here. This is
the AI prompt library that I made that
corresponds with the prompt builder. So,
what you can do here is one, edit the
prompt if you want to at all, but this
is just a completely randomized prompt,
and since I have random seed selected,
you can see here, if I just run this
again, it will make different prompts
every single time while keeping the
identity of my Laura attached to the
prompt. So, now let's say that I want to
save this prompt.
I can click save the library and it will
add that prompt here and I can load this
whenever I want by just clicking the
load. You can also create folders for
all of your prompts. So, let's say that
you have a different trigger word
assigned to some of the prompts. You can
just click new folder and name the
folder after whatever Laura you're
using. You can also add images to these
prompts folders as well. So, let's say
that I want to add this prompt to the
folder. I just type in that name there
and it will add one prompt to there. And
then we can run that again. I can save
that one.
We can run it again. I can save that
one. So, any good prompts that you get,
you can save and customize where they go
and add your own folders and so on. You
can also edit saved prompts so you can
move them to different folders if you
want. You can give them names and you
can change the text within the prompt.
One last thing that I'll point out for
both nodes is that the visual effects
are all customizable. You can turn them
off completely if you want to, but I'm
going to turn them back on. And you can
also select the color of whatever you
want the theme of your node pack to be.
So, yeah guys, that pretty much sums up
this entire node pack. We have covered
things like the character and Laura
section, the two different main modes
here. As you can see, we have some
different thumbnails here in the
business section. We have covered the
full categories and subcategories
section. And obviously I didn't go
through all of them because there's just
so many different things here. And just
kind of to add some context as to how
customizable these prompts are and how
many different types of prompts that you
can actually build with this. On screen
here is the total number of
possibilities that you can get out of
the professional / business prompt
building.
And on screen now is the total number of
possible prompts that you can get from
the influencer prompt building section.
Again, if you're wondering where to get
this, the link to the Patreon is in the
description of this video. If you guys
like this, please like the video and
subscribe. There is tons of more stuff
coming out soon. I got a lot planned.
And thanks for watching. Peace.